<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<!--
	Weapons
-->

<string_table>

	<string id="st_wpn_mp133">
		<text>MP-133</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp133_descr">
		<text>An evolution of the earlier IZh-81 pump action shotgun, the MP-133 was intended for civilian and security markets as a reliable and practical hunting and self-defence weapon.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmekh Mechanical Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_mp153">
		<text>MP-153</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_mp153_descr">
		<text>The first semi-automatic shotgun designed and manufactured by the Izhevsk Mechanical Plant, the MP-153 is one of the most popular semi-automatic shotguns of Russian origin and is widely used for various game hunting. Developed alongside the pump action MP-133 shotgun, it shares many of its parts and is known for its reliability and solid, heavy construction.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmekh Mechanical Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_wpn_mp153_m1">
        <text>MP-153 "Carabineer"</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_mp153_m1_descr">
		<text>The first semi-automatic shotgun designed and manufactured by the Izhevsk Mechanical Plant, the MP-153 is one of the most popular semi-automatic shotguns of Russian origin and is widely used for various game hunting. Developed alongside the pump action MP-133 shotgun, it shares many of its parts and is known for its reliability and solid, heavy construction. The "Carabineer" includes a muzzle break and Picatinny rail.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Izhmekh Mechanical Plant\n
		</text>
    </string>
<string id="st_wpn_ks23_vorkuta">
        <text>KS-23M "Vorkuta"</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wpn_ks23_vorkuta_descr">
		<text>At its core, the KS-23 is a manually-actuated, pump-action "shotgun" that fires unique 23mm shells. Though, while displaying an appearance more akin to a shotgun, the Russians designated the KS-23 as a "Special Carbine" due to its large-caliber rifled barrel when compared to the standard smoothbore barrels of conventional shotguns. The Vorkuta is a bigger version of the KS-23, featuring both a slimmed down 700mm barrel and pistol grip in pleace of the stand buttstock. The "Vorkuta" features a threaded barrel for introduction of a suppressor and attachable PU scope for better range combats. The weapon name suggests its origin might be from the city under the same name.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Tula Arms Plant\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[0,255,255,255] Extended tube, attachable Silencer and PU scope\n
		</text>
    </string>
	

	
</string_table>
