<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<!--
	WEAPON ATTACHMENTS
-->

<string_table>

	<string id="st_addon_scope">
		<text>PSO-1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_descr">
		<text>First introduced in the early 1960s, the PSO-1 became the iconic optic of the Soviet marksman. Issued alongside the SVD rifle, it saw widespread use across Eastern Europe and various Cold War conflicts. Its distinctive reticle combines a chevron for aiming with a built-in rangefinding scale, allowing shooters to quickly estimate distances without extra equipment.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union/Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]NPZ\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]4x\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Reticle illumination: %c[ui_gray_2]press Mark Switch key\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_addon_scope_1p29">
		<text>1P29 "Tyulpan"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_1p29_descr">
		<text>The 1P29 (aka UPO-1 / USP-1) is a universal sight made for Soviet/Russian small arms. Introduced in the 1980s, it is a compact, rugged prismatic optic (inspired by the British SUIT/Trilux designs), often fitted with a tritium/ambient illumination element and a stadiametric range scale for quick distance estimation; it saw service with late-Cold War and post-Soviet forces.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union/Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]NPZ\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]4x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_addon_scope_acog">
		<text>ACOG</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_acog_descr">
		<text>Advanced Combat Optical Gunsight — a rugged, compact prismatic sight built around a fixed-power tube and a battery-free illumination system (fiber-optic for daylight, tritium for low light). Beloved by many front-line units for its clarity and simplicity, certain ACOG reticles include bullet-drop compensation calibrated for specific rounds so shooters can make fast, first-round hits without dialing turrets. It's the sort of optic that feels like it was designed to be abused — hard, bright, and ready the moment you shoulder the weapon.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Trijicon\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]2.8x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_addon_scope_pso-1m2-01">
		<text>POSP 6x24</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_pso-1m2-01_descr">
		<text>A higher-magnification spin on the classic PSO formula, the POSP 6x24 was tailored as much for hunters and sport shooters as for military users. Its familiar chevron reticle and stadiametric scale make quick range estimates easy at game-hunting distances, and the slightly longer tube gives cleaner shots on small-to medium-sized targets. Built for export, the POSP found a wide civilian market — prized for its ruggedness, simple controls, and PSO-style ballistic aids that translate neatly from the field to the hunt.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Belarus\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Zenit-BelOMO\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]6x\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Reticle illumination: %c[ui_gray_2]press Mark Switch key\n \n	
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_addon_scope_specterDR">
		<text>SpecterDR</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_specterDR_descr">
		<text>Developed in the 1990s by Ernst Leitz Canada (ELCAN) for military contracts, the SpecterDR (Dual Role) is a rugged optic offering both a true 1x window for close-quarters and a 4x tube for mid-range engagements without swapping sights. A mechanical throw-lever on the side shifts the internal optics, toggling magnification while maintaining zero. Favored for its versatility, it is built to withstand hard use and make transitions seamless in combat.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Canada\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]ELCAN\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1x / 4x\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Reticle illumination: %c[ui_gray_2]press Mark Switch key\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_addon_scope_pso2">
		<text>PSO-1M2-1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_pso2_descr">
		<text>A modernized, compact offshoot of the classic PSO family adapted for special sniper platforms (notably the VSS/AS VAL) and short-to-medium ranges. The reticle and stadiametric markings are tuned for closer engagements (the rangefinder markings stop well short of the original 1000-m scale), and the body benefits from updated coatings and manufacturing tweaks for clearer glass and better low-light performance. It serves where the original PSO's long-range BDC is unnecessary — a practical, battlefield-ready optic for quieter, specialized rifles.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union/Belarus\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Zenit-BelOMO\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]4x\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Reticle illumination: %c[ui_gray_2]press Mark Switch key\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
		
	<string id="st_addon_scope_1p59">
		<text>1P59 "Giperon"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_1p59_descr">
		<text>A Russian variable-magnification sniper sight introduced around 2001 for modern SVD-class rifles. It features a crisp, thin reticle, bright image, and battery powered illumination.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]KMZ\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]3–10x\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Reticle illumination: %c[ui_gray_2]press Mark Switch key\n \n
		</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_addon_scope_1pn93">
		<text>1PN93</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_1pn93_descr">
		<text>A late Soviet-era night vision riflescope adapted and produced in the 1990s for a variety of rifles and light machine guns. It gives shooters usable target recognition and aiming capability in low-light conditions. The scope features a crisp, illuminated reticle and simple windage/elevation controls, making it practical for patrols and tactical operations. Designed to mount on standard dovetail rails, the 1PN93 balances clarity, reliability, and ease of use, providing effective performance for medium-range night engagements.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union/Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]NPZ\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1–4x\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Night Vision Toggle: %c[ui_gray_2]press Mark Switch key\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_addon_scope_leupold">
		<text>Mark 8 CQBSS LPVO</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_leupold_descr">
		<text>Built for military use under U.S. contracts, the Mark 8 CQBSS squeezes a 1–8x zoom into a compact, 34 mm-tube chassis, giving a low-power close-quarters window and a full 8x for longer shots. It uses a first-focal-plane LED-illuminated reticle for fast transitions and repeatable hits in mixed environments.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Leupold\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1–8x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_pn23">
		<text>PN-23</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_pn23_descr">
		<text>A variable night vision optic that doubles as a clip-on NV module for select sniper scopes. Lightweight but sturdy, it provides day/night flexibility: low-power settings for close work and a higher zoom for longer distances.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]NPZ\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1–6x\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Night Vision Toggle: %c[ui_gray_2]press Mark Switch key\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_addon_scope_marchf">
		<text>March-F 3x-24x52</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_marchf_descr">
		<text>A precision Japanese-made riflescope built for long-range work and fast transitions. The illuminated first-focal-plane reticle keeps the subtensions accurate across the range, while the large 52 mm objective and ED glass deliver high contrast and excellent light transmission.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Japan\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]DEON Optical Design\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]3–24x\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Reticle illumination: %c[ui_gray_2]press Mark Switch key\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_addon_scope_pgo7gs">
		<text>PGO-7</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_pgo7gs_descr">
		<text>A simple, purpose-built optic paired with the RPG-7 since the 1960s, the PGO-7 gives grenade crews a modest magnification and a ballistic reticle calibrated for common warheads. Compact and straightforward to use, it improves target ID and first-shot hits at extended ranges and was produced in several factories (with licensed copies abroad).\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]4x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_addon_scope_susat">
		<text>SUSAT</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_susat_descr">
		<text>Sight Unit Small Arms, Trilux — a British service optic developed in the late 1970s to give every rifleman a usable telescopic sight on the new SA80 family. Built with a simple, hard-wearing body and a tritium-illuminated aiming point for low-light use, the SUSAT became the standard sight for the L85/L86 and related weapons before later upgrades began to replace it.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United Kingdom\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Avimo\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]4x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_addon_scope_gauss_sight">
		<text>EOTS-62/ThermX Eliminator</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_gauss_sight_descr">
		<text>A rare Ukrainian thermal sight developed for specialized operations, offering 1–10x variable zoom in a compact, rugged housing. Its high-sensitivity thermal sensor provides rapid heat-signature detection through smoke, darkness, or cluttered environments. Built for precision and demanding careful maintenance, it was produced in very limited quantities for elite or experimental units.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Ukraine\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]REDACTED\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1–10x\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Thermal Toggle: %c[ui_gray_2]press Mark Switch key\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_addon_scope_1p78gs">
		<text>1P78 "Kashtan"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_1p78gs_descr">
		<text>A post-Soviet 2.8x combat sight developed in the 1990s by NPZ as a low-power replacement for older Soviet optics. It pairs a wide field of view with a tritium-illuminated chevron reticle calibrated for common AK rounds, favoring rapid target acquisition and practical accuracy at typical infantry distances. Lightweight and durable, the Kashtan is fitted to service rifles and squad weapons where fast, dependable aiming matters.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]NPZ\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]2.8x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_1pn93n2_1gs">
		<text>1PN93-1 Thermal</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_1pn93n2_1gs_descr">
		<text>A thermal reinterpretation of the 1PN93 family, it swaps the traditional image-intensifier tube for a mid-wave thermal sensor, turning heat signatures into a clear sight picture day or night. Heavier and more power-hungry than its NV cousins, it excels at spotting concealed or camouflaged targets through smoke and foliage and is typically issued in small numbers to reconnaissance and specialist sniper teams.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]NPZ\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]4x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_usp1">
		<text>1P29 "Tyulpan"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_usp1_descr">
		<text>The 1P29 (aka UPO-1 / USP-1) is a universal sight made for Soviet/Russian small arms. Introduced in the 1980s, it is a compact, rugged prismatic optic (inspired by the British SUIT/Trilux designs), often fitted with a tritium/ambient illumination element and a stadiametric range scale for quick distance estimation; it saw service with late-Cold War and post-Soviet forces.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]NPZ\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]4x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_addon_scope_trijicon_rmr">
		<text>ACOG + 1x RDS Kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_trijicon_rmr_descr">
		<text>A compact combat kit pairing a magnified ACOG with a canted 1x red-dot sight for fast transitions between close-quarters and mid-range engagements.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>	
	
	<string id="st_addon_scope_mark8_rmr">
		<text>Mark 8 CQBSS LPVO + 1x RDS Kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_mark8_rmr_descr">
		<text>A compact combat kit pairing the Leupold Mark 8 CQBSS low-power variable optic with a canted 1x red-dot for instant close-quarters aiming and sustained precision at longer ranges.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_spec_alt">
		<text>SpecterDR + 1x RDS Kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_spec_alt_descr">
		<text>A compact kit pairing the dual-role ELCAN SpecterDR with a canted red-dot for immediate reflex shots and quick switching to a magnified view for accurate follow-ups.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_addon_scope_kashtan_rmr">
		<text>Kashtan + 1x RDS Kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_kashtan_rmr_descr">
		<text>A low-power combat sight paired with a canted red-dot for instant close-quarters aiming and a quick switch to a stabilized magnified view for standard engagement distances.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_addon_scope_psicho_rmr">
		<text>PSO + 1x RDS Kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_psicho_rmr_descr">
		<text>Classic Dragunov-style PSO scope paired with a canted red-dot for rapid close-quarters response and a ready magnified sight for longer aimed shots.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_susatov"> <!-- It's not used in GAMMA 3DSS, so no flavor text -->
		<text>SUSAT</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_susatov_descr">
		<text>%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United Kingdom\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Avimo\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]4x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_march_f_shorty">
		<text>March-F Shorty LPVO</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_march_f_shorty_descr">
		<text>A compact Japanese low-power variable optic with a dual-focal-plane reticle, letting shooters maintain accurate holdovers across all zoom levels. It's the world's lightest and shortest scope with a 10x magnification.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Japan\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]DEON Optical Design\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1–10x\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Reticle illumination: %c[ui_gray_2]press Mark Switch key\n \n
		</text>		
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_march_f_shorty_alt">
		<text>March-F Shorty + 1x RDS Kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_march_f_shorty_alt_descr">
		<text>A compact kit pairing the March-F Shorty LPVO with a canted red-dot for instant close-quarters aiming and quick transition to magnified precision.\n \n
		</text>		
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_addon_scope_lco1">
		<text>LCO</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_lco1_descr">
		<text>Leupold Carbine Optic — a rugged red-dot sight designed for patrol rifles and carbines, featuring a crisp 1-MOA dot for precise close-quarters aiming and a wide viewing window for fast target acquisition. Built to be waterproof, fogproof, and shockproof, the LCO stands up to harsh field conditions while maintaining reliable performance.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Leupold\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_addon_scope_e0t2_mag">
		<text>Eotech XPS3 w/ Eotech 3x Magnifier</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_e0t2_mag_descr">
		<text>A compact holographic sight with a low-profile housing and intuitive controls for instinctive aiming at close range. Paired with a 3x flip-to-side magnifier, the kit lets the shooter quickly switch from reflex engagement to short-to-medium-range identification and precision follow-ups without changing optics.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]EOTech\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1x / 3x\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnifier flip: %c[ui_gray_2]set in MCM — Magnifier Switch\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	
	<string id="st_addon_scope_razor_mag">
		<text>UH-1 w/ Eotech 6x Magnifier</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_razor_mag_descr">
		<text>A fast 1x sight paired with a 6x flip-to-side magnifier, this kit gives immediate reflex aiming with a quick-on zoom for mid-range identification and follow-ups. Compact and modular, it keeps the primary sight usable when the magnifier is stowed and lets shooters extend engagement reach without swapping optics.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Vortex & EOTech\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1x / 6x\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnifier flip: %c[ui_gray_2]set in MCM — Magnifier Switch\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_addon_scope_razor">
		<text>Razor AMG UH-1 Gen. II</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_razor_descr">
		<text>Holographic sight with a precision reticle (1 MOA dot + rapid-lead ring), unlimited eye relief, NV-capable. Waterproof, fog- and shock-proof for brutal CQB use.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Vortex\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_exps3">
		<text>Eotech EXPS3</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_exps3_descr">
		<text>A compact holographic sight offering a selection of reticles designed for instinctive aiming in fast-paced engagements. The EXPS3 features side-mounted controls, a quick-detach mount, and a protective hood over the viewing window. Its design prioritizes speed and reliability, letting shooters engage targets rapidly without adjusting eye position, while built-in ruggedness ensures consistent performance under field stress.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]EOTech\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1x\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Reticle switch: %c[ui_gray_2]press Mark Switch key\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
  
	<string id="st_addon_scope_he510">
		<text>Holosun HE510C</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_he510_descr">
		<text>The Holosun HE510C is an open red-dot sight. It features a 2 MOA dot and 65 MOA circle reticle, offering quick target acquisition and precision aiming. Built with an aluminum housing and titanium hood, it ensures durability and shock resistance. The sight includes a quick-detach mount for easy installation and removal.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States/China\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Holosun\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1x\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Reticle switch: %c[ui_gray_2]press Mark Switch key\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
  
	<string id="st_addon_scope_bravo4">
		<text>BRAVO4</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_bravo4_descr">
		<text>A fixed 4x magnification prism sight designed for modern battle rifles. Its wide field of view facilitates rapid target acquisition and situational awareness. The sight features a horseshoe-dot reticle calibrated for 5.56/7.62 NATO rounds, and is built with a lightweight, durable magnesium housing. It often comes with a red-dot sight mounted on top for instant close-quarters aiming.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Sig Sauer\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]4x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
  
	<string id="st_addon_scope_hamr">
		<text>Mark 4 HAMR</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_hamr_descr">
		<text>The Leupold Mark 4 HAMR (High Accuracy Multi-Range) 4x24 is a tactical fixed-power scope tailored for mid-range precision shooting. Its standout feature is the integrated DeltaPoint red-dot sight mounted atop the scope, allowing for rapid target acquisition in close quarters while maintaining accuracy at extended ranges. The scope boasts a rugged aluminum housing, Argon/Krypton gas blend for fogproofing, and lens coatings for enhanced durability and clarity. With a 4x magnification and an illuminated CM-R2 reticle, it's optimized for 5.56 NATO platforms, though it excels with various calibers. Designed for military and law enforcement applications, the HAMR offers a compact solution for versatile combat scenarios.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Leupold\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]4x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
  
	<string id="st_addon_scope_razorhd">
		<text>Razor II HD LPVO</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_razorhd_descr">
		<text>The Vortex Razor II HD-E 1-6x24 is a high-performance LPVO built for speed and precision. Its 1-6x magnification allows rapid engagement from close quarters to mid-range targets. The second focal plane reticle keeps holdovers consistent, and the illuminated reticle ensures fast target acquisition. Rugged and reliable, it excels in dynamic combat scenarios.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Vortex\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1–6x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_addon_scope_devo">
		<text>D-EVO + LCO</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_devo_descr">
		<text>The Leupold D-EVO Offset Prism Optic combined with the LCO red-dot offers a unique dual-optic system designed for rapid target acquisition and mid-range precision. The D-EVO is a 6x magnified prism sight that mounts offset to the side of a primary red-dot sight, such as the LCO, allowing shooters to transition seamlessly between close-quarters engagements and longer-range targets. Together, these optics offer a compact and efficient solution for dynamic shooting scenarios.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Leupold\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1x (LCO)/ 6x (D-EVO)\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Reticle illumination: %c[ui_gray_2]press Mark Switch key\n \n
		</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_addon_scope_side">
		<text>Side-Mount Telescope</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_side_descr">
		<text>A side-mounted telescope designed for lever-action rifles, preserving the rifle’s classic profile while providing a long sight radius. The optic uses a straightforward reticle and reliable internals, reflecting early 20th-century design rather than modern tactical features.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Winchester or contemporary period optics makers\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]4x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_romeo"> <!-- Not sure if it's even used in GAMMA; only the romeo4 and romeo8 are used -->
		<text>Sig Sauer ROMEO4</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_romeo_descr">
		<text>%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Sig Sauer\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_cortex_scope">
		<text>Razor HD Gen III 1-10x LPVO</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cortex_scope_desc">
		<text>The Vortex Razor HD Gen III 1-10x24 is a premium first focal plane LPVO designed for versatility and precision. It offers a true 1x magnification for close-quarters engagements and extends to 10x for mid-range targets. The scope features an HD optical system with fully multi-coated lenses, providing exceptional clarity and light transmission. Its rugged construction ensures durability in demanding conditions, making it suitable for military, law enforcement, and competitive shooting applications.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Vortex\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1–10x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_cmore">
        <text>C-MORE Railway Tactical</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_scope_cmore_descr">
		<text>The C-MORE Railway Red Dot Sight is a versatile, open-reflex optic designed for rapid target acquisition across various platforms. It offers an unlimited field of view, eliminating the tunnel vision common in tube-style optics. The sight mounts directly to Weaver or Picatinny rails, making it compatible with shotguns, rifles, handguns, and more. Its detachable rail base allows for easy installation and removal, enhancing its adaptability for different shooting scenarios.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]C-MORE Systems\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1x\n \n
		</text>
    </string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_zf4">
		<text>ZF-4 Scope</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_zf4_descr">
		<text>A compact 4x telescopic sight issued late in WWII for semi-automatic and bolt-action German service rifles — most famously fitted to the G43/K43 and seen on some K98k examples with swept-back mounts. Simple, rugged optics with a 3-post (or crosshair) reticle and factory elevation preset around 300 m, built for quick engagement rather than long-range precision. Wartime production was by several German firms (Voigtlander among them), so markings and minor details vary between examples.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Germany\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]4x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_kp_sr2">
		<text>KP-SR2</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_kp_sr2_descr">
		<text>Compact open-reflex sight developed in the 1990s for the SR-2 / SR-2M "Veresk" family, optimized for the short receiver and folding-stock layout. Its low-profile, rugged housing preserves a small footprint while providing quick target acquisition via a simple red-dot reticle.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]TsNIITochMash\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1x\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Reticle switch: %c[ui_gray_2]press Mark Switch key\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_gee36">
		<text>ZF 3x Optic (G36 carry-handle)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_gee36_descr">
		<text>Derived from the G36's carry-handle sighting module, this compact telescopic optic functions as a standalone mid-range scope when mounted on a Picatinny rail. Simple reticle, rugged housing, and combat-grade construction make it suited for quick transitions between close and medium ranges while retaining the original sight's durability. Originally produced for the G36 by Hensoldt (Zeiss lineage), the unit is commonly found repurposed or adapted for other platforms.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Germany\n\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Hensoldt (produced for Heckler & Koch)\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]3x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_t12">
		<text>T12W 30Hz Thermal</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_t12_descr">
		<text>Compact weapon-mounted thermal imager offering a 30 Hz refresh rate from an 80x60 FLIR Lepton sensor. Provides a false-color image polarity, on-screen reticle overlay and quick-detach Picatinny mounting for weapon or handheld use, but the small sensor limits fine identification to short–mid ranges. Built in a metal, O-ring sealed housing with on-board image processing and battery operation for rugged low-visibility scanning.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Torrey Pines Logic\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_addon_scope_bossxe">
        <text>BOSS-Xe</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_addon_scope_bossxe_descr">
		<text>The Wilcox BOSS Xe is a high-power laser aiming device designed for military and law enforcement applications. It features a fully integrated optical bench that houses a smart red-dot sight, visible and near-infrared lasers, and a backup iron sight, all co-aligned. This system allows users to quickly switch between two preset ballistic trajectories without re-zeroing the weapon.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Wilcox Industries\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1x\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Reticle switch: %c[ui_gray_2]press Mark Switch key\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] %c[ui_gray_2]Laser Toggle\n \n
		</text>
    </string>
	

	<string id="st_addon_scope_lazup_generic">
		<text>Laser Aiming Module</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_lazup_generic_descr">
		<text>\n \n%c[ui_gray_2]COMPATIBILITY:\n \n%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] Multiple weapons with picatinny or compatible rail.\n \n %c[ui_gray_1] Used for aimed shooting from any position. Can be used with NVGs for easier targeting.\n </text>
	</string>
	

	<string id="st_addon_scope_pk1_obzor">
		<text>PK-1 "Obzor" (1P63)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_pk1_obzor_descr">
		<text>Compact 1x collimator sight developed in the late 1980s for AK-pattern weapons with a side-mount interface; rugged, utilitarian styling suits close-quarters and short-range work. It operates without conventional batteries (ambient-light/solar collection with tritium illumination for low light) and offers simple day/night reticle modes and a contrast filter for bright conditions. Produced by the Novosibirsk Instrument-Building Plant (NPZ) to a military specification (development at TsKB "Tochpribor"), it's commonly seen in modern Russian service and civilian variants.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]NPZ/TsKB Tochpribor\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_addon_scope_pk6">
		<text>PK-06</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_pk6_descr">
		<text>Compact open-reflex sight produced by BelOMO. The PK-06 is a 1x red-dot style optic with automatic brightness adjustment, selectable reticle patterns, and an improved drainage/sealing design compared with earlier PK-05 variants — built for simple, rugged use on Picatinny/Weaver rails. Widely offered by Eastern European suppliers and discussed in optics reviews, it serves as a lightweight, budget-minded combat/sport reflex sight.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Belarus\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]BelOMO\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1x\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Reticle switch: %c[ui_gray_2]press Mark Switch key\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_pilad_p1x42">
		<text>Pilad P1x42</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_pilad_p1x42_descr">
		<text>Open-reflex red-dot sight from the Pilad line, built around a large 34–42 mm viewing window for an expansive field of view and fast target acquisition. Offers selectable reticle patterns and a small, rugged aluminum body suited to hunting and service use; commonly supplied with Weaver/Picatinny or dovetail mounts. Manufactured under the VOMZ/Pilad brand in Russia and marketed as a no-frills, robust reflex option for short-range work.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]VOMZ\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1x\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Reticle switch: %c[ui_gray_2]press Mark Switch key\n \n
		</text>	
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_1p87">
		<text>PK-120 (1P87)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_1p87_descr">
		<text>Modern Russian open-reflex sight with a holographic-style reticle, designed for rapid target acquisition at close to mid ranges. Rugged housing and wide field of view make it suitable for both military and law-enforcement small arms applications, and it mounts on standard Picatinny interfaces.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Valday\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_pilad_p4x32">
		<text>Pilad P4x32</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_pilad_p4x32_descr">
		<text>Fixed-power riflescope from VOMZ's Pilad line, built as a simple, rugged optic with an illuminated reticle option and a wide viewing window for quick target acquisition at short–to–medium ranges. Commonly fitted to hunting and service rifles, the design emphasizes durability and user-adjustable illumination rather than advanced tactical features.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]VOMZ\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]4x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_po4x34">
		<text>PO4x34</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_po4x34_descr">
		<text>Fixed-power telescopic sight produced for Russian bullpup and specialized rifles (notably the OTs-14 "Groza"). Often fitted to the Groza with a purpose-made bracket, genuine examples were manufactured by the Zagorsk Optical-Mechanical Plant (ZOMZ) in the 1990s and show up in collector/sales listings as a period Russian optic.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]ZOMZ\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]4x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_valday_ps320">
		<text>PS-320</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_valday_ps320_descr">
		<text>A Russian take on the Elcan SpecterDR concept: a rugged dual-mode combat sight pairing a low-profile 1x window with a magnified 6x prism, switchable on the fly without re-zeroing. Built for mechanical reliability and quick transitions, it favors stout construction, simple selector controls and broad reticle holds suited to assault-rifle ergonomics rather than elaborate electronics.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Valday\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1x / 6x\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Reticle illumination: %c[ui_gray_2]press Mark Switch key\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_burris_tac30">
		<text>TAC30 LPVO</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_burris_tac30_descr">
		<text>Compact low-powered variable optic tuned for close-quarters speed and practical mid-range work. The 1–4x range and a ballistic-style CQ reticle (calibrated around 5.56) allow fast transitions between hip-level engagements and aimed fire at moderate distances, while the wide field of view favors target tracking in dynamic encounters. Rugged construction and simple controls make it an affordable, no-nonsense LPVO for general combat use.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Burris\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1–4x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>		

	<string id="st_addon_scope_romeo4">
		<text>ROMEO4</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_romeo4_descr">
		<text>Compact 1x red-dot sight in a sealed tube housing, built to military durability standards. What sets it apart from more basic red-dots are its selectable reticle patterns (dot, circle, or combined) and NVG-compatible brightness settings, making it versatile for both day and night use.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Sig Sauer\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1x\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Reticle switch: %c[ui_gray_2]press Mark Switch key\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_addon_scope_romeo8">
		<text>ROMEO8</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_romeo8_descr">
		<text>Full-size enclosed red-dot sight designed for carbines and rifles, offering a noticeably larger viewing window than compact tube optics. Its main distinction from the ROMEO4 line is the oversized housing and generous sight picture, combined with selectable reticle options (dot, circle, or combinations) and NVG-compatible brightness settings. Built to handle heavy recoil and hard use, it fills the role of a robust combat-grade optic for rapid engagement at short to medium ranges.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Sig Sauer\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1x\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Reticle switch: %c[ui_gray_2]press Mark Switch key\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_aim_acro">
		<text>ACRO P-1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_aim_acro_descr">
		<text>Advanced Compact Reflex Optic — compact enclosed-emitter sight engineered for pistols and PDWs; the sealed optical channel protects the emitter and electronics from debris and slide impact. It uses a 3.5-MOA dot, offers multiple brightness levels including NVG-compatible settings, and is built to withstand heavy recoil and harsh environments.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Sweden\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Aimpoint\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_addon_scope_specter_hco">
		<text>Specter HCO</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_specter_hco_descr">
		<text>Holographic Combat Optic — prototype sight from ELCAN, using a laser-projected reticle similar to EOTech sights but housed in a solid, fully sealed aluminum body for durability. Offers a large viewing window with a circle-dot reticle, featuring three short subtension lines inside the 72 MOA circle and a 1 MOA center dot. It was designed for rugged, combat-ready use, though it remains a prototype and never saw mass production.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Canada\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]ELCAN\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_monstrum_2x32">
		<text>Monstrum 2x32 Compact</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_monstrum_2x32_descr">
		<text>Compact prism scope that delivers true fixed-power magnification in a short, rugged package. Etched prism reticle with illumination for low-light holds makes fast target acquisition and quick follow-ups straightforward; the sight favors simple, practical reticles over complicated ballistic calculators. Low-profile housing mounts on Picatinny rails and is suited for carbines and short-to-mid-range rifles where a snag-free, durable optic is preferred.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Monstrum Tactical\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]2x\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Reticle illumination: %c[ui_gray_2]press Mark Switch key\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_trihawk_3x30">
		<text>Trihawk 3x30</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_trihawk_3x30_descr">
		<text>A compact fixed-power optic with unusually wide field of view for a 3x scope. Its etched reticle remains usable even without illumination, making it dependable in harsh conditions. Built into a rugged prism housing, it's designed for fast target acquisition on carbines while still giving precise shot placement at intermediate distances.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Swampfox Optics\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]3x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_ncstar_ado">
		<text>ADO P4 Sniper</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_ncstar_ado_descr">
		<text>The NcSTAR ADO P4 Sniper 3–9x42 Riflescope is a variable magnification optic featuring an integrated red-dot sight. The red-dot lens flips up to the deployed position and automatically turns on with the push of a button, and flips down to the stored position to turn off. It includes an auto-locking quick release mount compatible with Weaver and Picatinny rails.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]NcSTAR\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1x (red-dot) / 3–9x (scope)\n \n
		</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_addon_scope_vulcan">
		<text>Vulcan 3.5x Alpha MG Compact NV</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_vulcan_descr">
		<text>Compact Gen-3 night vision riflescope offering a true 3.5x magnification in a short, rugged housing built for weapon mounting. Features manual/automatic gain control, an internal reticle with illumination, and provisions for long-range IR illumination and remote control—designed as a hands-on, combat-grade NV module rather than a precision daylight optic.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Armasight\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]3.5x\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Night Vision Toggle: %c[ui_gray_2]press Mark Switch key\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_echo1">
		<text>ECHO1 1-2x30mm Thermal</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_echo1_descr">
		<text>Compact thermal reflex sight combining a 1x reflex-like view with digital zoom up to 2x in a short, weapon-mounted package. Uses a low-resolution uncooled VOx thermal array with a 30 Hz refresh rate, giving clear hot-target imagery at short-to-mid ranges even in total darkness; onboard controls and a Picatinny mount make it quick to fit to carbines and PDWs. Lightweight and ruggedized for field use, the sight is optimized for target detection and acquisition rather than fine optical resolution.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Sig Sauer\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1x-2x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_addon_scope_skeet">
		<text>OASYS SkeetIRx</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_skeet_descr">
		<text>Compact clip-on thermal monocular that converts day sniper scopes into a thermal sight; designed to mount in front of an existing optic. Features a true 1x base view with digital zoom options and a 640-resolution thermal sensor — optimized for target detection and acquisition rather than fine optical detail.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Trijicon\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]1x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>	

	<string id="st_addon_scope_c79">
		<text>C79</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_c79_descr">
		<text>Compact 3.4x optical sight developed by Ernst Leitz Canada (ELCAN) and adopted as the standard optics package for the C7/C8 family of rifles — built to be a rugged, combat-ready mid-range scope with a simple illuminated reticle and practical hold marks tuned for 5.56. Its sealed aluminum housing and straightforward adjustment layout made it popular with military units from the 1980s onward, and it became a workhorse prism/optic on NATO-style carbines long before low-power variable optics became common. The C79's lineage later fed into Elcan's Specter line of dual-mode optics, so its design DNA shows up in several modern combat sights.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Canada\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]ELCAN\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Magnification: %c[ui_gray_2]3.4x\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_up_binoc_d1_descr">
		<text>Experimental upgrade that allows the binoculars to detect and mark living beings within their field of view.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_sup_new">
		<text>Special Upgrade Pack</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_sup_new_descr">
		<text>%c[0,255,255,255]KIT INCLUDES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • Various tools, parts and attachments for upgrading a selection of guns.\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_addon_scope_mag">
		<text>Eotech Magnifier</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_addon_scope_mag_descr">
		<text>Compact magnifier designed to give short-to-mid-range reach when paired with a red-dot or holographic sight. Features a fixed magnification and the flip-to-side mount for fast transition between magnified and unmagnified shots — widely used and even selected by special operations units.\n \n
		%c[0,255,255,255]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[0,255,255,255] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]United States\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[0,255,255,255] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]EOTech\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[0,255,255,255] Combine with with an EOTech XPS3 for 3x magnification or a Vortex UH-1 for 6x.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>	
	
</string_table>
